sloyalty.com 2017-06-08

# Privacy Policy - S Loyalty

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Privacy Policy describes the collection of personal information by Visual Squares LTD (the “Company”, “we”, “us”) from users of our Website at www.sloyalty.com (the “Website”), as well as all related software, tools, systems, programs and other services provided by us (collectively, together with the Website, the “Services”). This Policy also describes our use and disclosure of that information. By using our Service, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Policy is incorporated by reference into the Company Terms of Use (//www.sloyalty.com/terms-conditions) and subject to the provisions of the Terms of Use.

## Personal Information

“Personal Information,” as used in this Policy, is information that specifically identifies an individual, such as an individual’s name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. Personal Information also includes information about an individual’s activities, such as information about his or her purchase history, and demographic information, such as date of birth, gender, geographic area, and preferences, when any of this information is linked to Personal Information that identifies that individual.

Personal Information may also include information about your computer hardware and software including your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information may be automatically collected by us and is used for the operation of our service, maintenance of service quality and provision of general statistics regarding use of the Services.

Personal Information does not include “aggregate” or other non-personally identifiable information. Aggregate information is information that we collect about a group or category of products, services, or users that is not personally identifiable or from which individual identities are removed. We may use and disclose aggregate information, and other non-personally identifiable information, for various purposes.

## Collection of Personal Information

We collect Personal Information that our users provide to us in a variety of ways through our Services, including:

  *  _E-mail Newsletters_. We may offer e-mail newsletters with announcements and information about the Company from time to time on our Services. If you sign up to receive a newsletter from us, we collect your e-mail address. You may opt out of receiving e-mail newsletters.
  *  _User Accounts and Profiles_. Our Services gives you the ability to register for an account or to create and update a user profile on the Services. We will collect the Personal Information that you provide to us in the course of using that functionality. This information may include, for example, your name, contact information, and system information, as well as information about your interests, preferences and future needs. We may indicate that some personal information is required for you to register for the account or to create the profile.
  *  _Integrated Service_. You may be given the option to access or register for the Service through the use of your user name and passwords for certain services provided by third parties (each an “Integrated Service”), such as through the use of your BigCommerce credentials or through Shopify programming interfaces (APIs). We may also ask you to change the settings in the Integrated Service in order for our Services to connect to the Integrated Service. By doing this, you authorize us to access and store the credentials you provide, your name, email address(es), date of birth, gender, current city, and other information that the Integrated Service makes available to us, including all Personal Information and other information relating to your customers, and to use and disclose it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You should check the Integrated Service’s privacy settings to understand and change the information sent to us through such Integrated Service. Please review each Integrated Service’s terms of use and privacy policies carefully before using their services and connecting to our Services.
  *  _Correspondence_. If you contact us by e-mail, using a contact form on the Services, or by mail, fax, or other means, we collect the Personal Information contained within, and associated with, your correspondence. We use this Personal Information to respond to your correspondence. We may also use your correspondence to improve the Services.
  *  _Promotions_. We or our advertisers and other business partners may conduct or sponsor special contests, sweepstakes, and other promotions that users may enter or otherwise participate in our Services. Certain of these promotions may be co-branded with one of our advertisers or other business partners. In these instances, the collection of your Personal Information may occur directly by the third-party partner on its website or other online service and may be shared with us. The promotion will state the privacy policy or policies governing the collection of such personal information.
  *  _Referrals_. Part of the Services enables end users to refer other individuals to merchants using our Services. You must only provide us with addresses of individuals whom you believe might have an interest in the merchant you are referring. We will use email addresses provided to us to send the referral messages and to report the email addresses used for the referral to the applicable merchant.

## Passive Information Collection

  * When you visit our Services, some information is collected automatically. For example, when you access our Service, we automatically collect certain information, which may include your browser’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type, the nature of the device from which you are visiting the Services (e.g., a personal computer or a mobile device), the identifier for any handheld or mobile device that you may be using, the Web site that you visited immediately prior to accessing any Web-based Services, the actions you take on our Services, and the content, features, and activities that you access and participate in on our Services. We also may collect information regarding your interaction with e-mail messages, such as whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded a message.
  * We may collect this information passively using technologies such as standard server logs, cookies, and clear GIFs (also known as “Web beacons”). We use passively-collected information to administer, operate, and improve the Website and our other Services and systems, to improve the effectiveness of advertising on our Services, and to provide advertisements and other content that is tailored to you. If we link or associate any information gathered through passive means with Personal Information, or if applicable laws require us to treat any information gathered through passive means as Personal Information, we treat the combined information as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. Otherwise, we use and disclose information collected by passive means in aggregate form or otherwise in a non-personally identifiable form.
  * Also, please be aware that third parties, such as companies displaying advertisements on the Service, or sites or services provided by third parties (“Third-Party Sites”) that may be linked to or from the Service, may set cookies on your hard drive or use other means of passively collecting information about your use of their services, Third-Party Sites or content. We do not have access to, or control over, these third-party means of passive data collection.

## Use of your Personal Information

We use Personal Information that we have collected in several ways, including:

  * Company collects and uses your Personal Information and the Personal Information of others you have provided to us to operate the Website and deliver the Services you have requested.
  * Company may also use your Personal Information to inform you of other products or services available from Company and its affiliates. We may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
  * Company may keep track of the web pages our users visit within the Website, in order to assess and improve Company services. This data may be used to deliver customized content and advertising within Company to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
  * We use Personal Information to provide the services and information that you request. We also use your Personal Information to enhance, improve, operate, analyze and maintain our Services and other systems (e.g., to troubleshoot problems); to prevent fraudulent use of our Services and other systems; to prevent or take action against activities that are, or may be, in violation of our Terms of Use or applicable law; to tailor advertisements, content, and other aspects of your experience on and in connection with the Services; to maintain a record of our dealings with you; for other administrative purposes (e.g., contacting you regarding administrative information or notices); to resolve disputes and enforce our agreements with you; and for any other purposes that we may disclose to you at the point at which we request your Personal Information, and pursuant to your consent.

Company will not otherwise transfer, sell, rent or trade your Personal Information to third parties for direct marketing purposes without your written consent.

## Disclosure of your Personal Information

We disclose Personal Information that we have collected in several ways, including:

  * Company may share Personal Information with its affiliates and trusted partners including but not limited to, data processors which help the Company: perform statistical analysis, provide hosting/computing or infrastructure services, send you email or postal mail, or provide customer support. All such third parties are prohibited from using your Personal Information except to provide these services to Company, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your Personal Information.
  * Company will also disclose your Personal Information, without notice, if required to do so by any applicable laws, rules, regulations, codes and or guidelines or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Company or the Services; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Company; (c) the enforcement of our agreements; and, (d) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services, or the public.
  * Company may disclose Personal Information to third-party service providers (e.g., value-added resellers, payment processors, data storage and processing facility vendors) that assist us in our work. We limit the Personal Information provided to these service providers to that which is reasonably necessary for them to perform their functions, and we require them to agree to maintain the confidentiality of such Personal Information.
  * Information about our users, including Personal Information, may be disclosed and otherwise transferred to an acquirer, or successor or assignee as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, or similar transaction, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which Personal Information is transferred to one or more third parties as one of our business assets.

## Use of Cookies

The Website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Company pages, or register with the Website or Services, a cookie helps the Website to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information. When you return to the same Company website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Website features that you customized.

We may also rely on or permit third-party companies to display ads tailored to your interests on third-party websites. These third-party companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior on the Website. Each of these companies uses the information it collects according to its own privacy and security policies. If you wish to not have this information used by third parties for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> to opt-out.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Website or Services.

## Security of your Personal Information

Company secures your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We use reasonable security measures that are designed to protect Personal Information from accidental loss, disclosure, misuse, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that no data security measures can be guaranteed to be completely effective. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you provide to us. You transmit information to us at your own risk. You are responsible for all Personal Information submitted through your account or user profile and all actions taken through your account and user profile.

## International Visitors

Our servers and data centers may not be located in the same country from which you access our Services. If you choose to use the Services, then you should know that you may be transferring your Personal Information outside of your region and into other countries, which might include the United States, for storage and processing. By providing your Personal Information to us through your use of the Services, you agree to that transfer, storage, and processing outside of your jurisdiction. Also, we may transfer your data from other countries, including the United States, to other countries or regions in connection with storage and processing of data, fulfilling your requests, and operating the Services. You should know that each region can have its own privacy and data security laws, some of which may be less stringent as compared to those of your own region.

## Children Under Thirteen

Our Terms of Use prohibit users of the Services who are under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13 on our Services, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we may have collected any such Personal Information on our Services, please notify us at [privacy@sloyalty.com](mailto:privacy@sloyalty.com).

## Changes to this Policy

We may occasionally update this Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the beginning of the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Service after such changes will be subject to the then-current policy. If we change this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially less restrictive of our use or disclosure of your Personal Information, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of the change and to obtain your consent prior to applying the change to any Personal Information that we collected from you prior to the date the change becomes effective. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we collect, use, and disclose Personal Information.

## Access and Correction of your Personal Information

You have the right to ask us if we hold any personal information about you and if so, to request a copy of some or all of your Personal Information. You also have the right to ask us to correct your personal information which you consider as inaccurate. Please send your request and any comments you may have regarding this Privacy Policy to [privacy@sloyalty.com](mailto:privacy@sloyalty.com).

## Unsubscribe from Newsletters

We respect your privacy and you may, at any time and without charge, request Company to cease using your personal information for direct marketing purposes by writing to Company at [unsubscribe@sloyalty.com](mailto:unsubscribe@sloyalty.com). We also give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of email newsletters via the “unsubscribe” link provided in the email newsletter.

Effective as of January 15, 2014
